roomkey.com 2019-06-16

# Privacy Statement - Roomkey

Our Privacy Policy is an extension of our commitment to provide quality services with integrity to our customers. The Policy is designed to assist you in understanding how we collect, use and safeguard the information you may provide to us and to assist you in making informed decisions when using the Roomkey website (the “Site”). By visiting the Site, you are expressly consent to the collection, use, sharing, storage, processing and disclosure of information as described in this Privacy Policy.

### Types of Information We Collect

When you visit our Site we may store information obtained or provided during your web session. We may also assign you one or more “cookies”. Our Site utilizes cookies to collect for, among other things, general Site and web usage patterns. Information gathered from cookies may include the date and time of visits, the Site pages viewed, time spent at our Site and the websites that you visited before and after your visit to our Site. Our Site’s servers also automatically identify your computer by its Internet protocol (“IP”) address, which is a unique string of numbers that is assigned to your computer by your Internet service provider. Your IP address may be used to address problems with our server, administer our Site and/or to gather broad demographic information about our users. In addition, the other websites that you visit have IP addresses, and we may collect the IP addresses of those websites and their pages.

The majority of browsers accept cookies, but the “Help” menu on your browser should give you options for preventing, accepting, or receiving notice of new cookies. However, please be aware that if you block cookies, some Site functionality may be lost. If you wish to opt-out of the display of targeted advertisements, you may do so by clicking [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/) to visit the Network Advertising Initiative site to set preferences and opt out of third-party targeting cookies used by vendors including Google, Turn and others. Please note this does not opt you out of being served advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads.

In addition to the information we collect using cookies, we also collect information, including personally identifiable information, that you actively provide directly to us. For example, through an account created on this Site or communications (such as emails) you may send to us. We may maintain your email and the information therein, including your e-mail address and any personally identifiable information contained in the e-mail. Information collected in this manner is subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

In addition to the information you provide to us, and what is provided through cookies, we may receive, collect or record various types of hardware and software information. Such information can include technical or functional information such as interface type, software types and applications, communications data and communications details. Periodically, we may work with contracted third parties to help us evaluate the effectiveness of our site. This activity may (or may not) include the capture of user screen videos, click data, page scrolling data, and character entry. In these cases, no personally identifiable information is captured or retained, and the only use of this information is to help us make the site function more effectively. Specifically, we do not use this information to identify you in any way or to help sell specific products or deals, and we do not share this information in any way with any commercial or non-commercial partner of Roomkey.

Any information you provide directly or indirectly to us (other than personally identifiable information), whether by direct entry, submission, e-mail, or otherwise (including data, questions, comments, or suggestions), will be treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary and will become the property of Hotel JV Services, LLC (the “Company”). Such information may be used for any lawful purpose, including, but not limited to disclosure, transmission, publication, broadcast, commercial dissemination, and posting. The Company shall be free to use any ideas, concepts, know-how, or techniques contained in any communication you send to us for any purpose whatsoever, including, but not limited to, developing and marketing services using such information.

### Use of Collected Information

The information we collect is used for various business purposes. For example, we may use the information collected to enhance our Site to make it easier, faster and more effective to use. In addition, we may use information to customize a user’s Site experience to better suit the user’s needs, and to develop our services. Additionally, cookies provide us information about how many people visit our Site, when they visit and how they use our Site. We may also use the information collected to collaborate with other businesses in order to drive relevant content to you. Information collected may result in your viewing of particular advertising tailored to your interests based on your activities on our Site and a shopping experience customized to you in content and services.

Our goal is to provide you with the most recent and compelling information to help you qualify your hotel booking decisions. To that end we may email you about destinations and/or hotels that may interest you, based on the information you have provided — whether directly or indirectly. With each email you receive, you will have the opportunity to choose not to receive future email correspondence. We also may share similar content with you via social media channels, like Facebook, if you have provided us with your social media contact information.

We use a marketing company to manage our advertising on other sites. This marketing company may use technologies such as cookies, clear gifs, and tags to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to not have this information used for the purpose of serving you interest-based ads, you may opt-out by visiting <http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/>. We use Google AdSense to publish ads on other sites. You may opt-out of the use of this cookie by visiting Google’s Advertising and Privacy page: <http://www.google.com/settings/ads>.

### We May Share Your Information

We may share your information with our members, commercial partners, affiliates, or other third parties; including with third parties that perform services on our behalf. We may also authorize third parties to collect information on our behalf. We, these companies, and other third parties may use information about your visits to this and other websites and other information you provide in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. We may also disclose your information: (i) to investigate, prevent or take other actions with respect to illegal or fraudulent activities; (ii) in response to subpoenas or court orders, or as we otherwise believe in good faith to be required by law; and (iii) to protect or defend our property or rights, or the property and rights of others.

### Your Account and Online Password

You may create an account to become an online member of Roomkey at your election. Membership will allow you to save Site preferences, and you will be able to provide, update, and change certain of your information online through your account. To become an online member, you will have to provide your e-mail address and create a password.

We may use and share information you provide to us through your account in the same manner that we may use your other information, as described in this Privacy Policy; however, we will never disclose, share, or sell your password.

Once your account is created, you will be able to log in to your account using your e-mail address and password. Account access will allow you to access information related to your accounts and in certain cases, special offerings or other information available to those individuals who have set-up an account on Roomkey.

Please note that all information and other content you access using your account (including, without limitation, your password) is, and must be treated as, strictly confidential proprietary information and a trade secret of the Company. Accordingly, such content or information must not be disclosed and must be protected using no less than commercially reasonable means of protection. In order to help us protect the content and information you access using your account, you must not disclose your password to anyone and must make sure that your password is secure.

### We Secure Your Information

We secure the sensitive information you provide (such as passwords) by using reasonable technical efforts to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, or accidental loss or destruction of information. Although we use commercially reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of user data, transmissions made using the internet cannot be made absolutely secure. We have no liability for disclosure of user data due to errors in transmission or unauthorized acts of third parties.

### LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES

Our Privacy Policy applies only to your use of this Site. The Site contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of those websites. Links to other websites do not imply an endorsement of the materials or policies on those websites. You should read the privacy policies of each website you visit to determine what information that website may be collecting about you, and how they use that information.

### Our Website is Located in the United States

Our servers are located in the United States and our Site is intended for customers located in the United States. If you are accessing our Site from outside the United States, you agree that any information provided may be transferred to, processed and stored in the United States. United States privacy, data protection and other laws may be different and/or less comprehensive than those of your own jurisdiction. By accessing or using the Site, you expressly consent to the collection, processing, use and disclosure of your information in the United States as described in this Privacy Policy.

### Changes to the Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may be updated periodically and posted on the Site, and applies to the online practices of Hotel JV Services, LLC. References to “we”, “us” and “our” are references to Hotel JV Services, LLC. We reserve the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time, without notice, by posting revisions on the Site. You agree to review the Privacy Policy each time you use the Site so that you are aware of any modifications. By accessing or using the Site, you agree to be bound by all of the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy as posted at the time of your access or use.

### California Privacy Rights

If you are a resident of the State of California, you have the right to, on an annual basis, request information related to parties with whom we have shared your personally identifiable information for those third parties’ marketing purposes during the previous calendar year. You may obtain such information by contacting us as set forth below.

### Contact Us

This Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference in and is a part of our Terms of Use Agreement. If you have questions about our privacy practices, please contact us at [feedback@roomkey.com](mailto:feedback@roomkey.com).

 _Effective as of November 5, 2015._
